A Finding Aid to the William Chapin Seitz Papers, circa 1930-1995, in the Archives of American Art AAA.seitwill
Archives of American Art
- Artwork, circa 1950s-1972; Series 8; 6 Folders Box 32, 33
  - Phil Elliott, Pencil on Paper Sketch, circa 1960 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Miscellanous and Unidentified Artworks, circa 1950s; 2 Folders (Box 32, Folder 38-39)
    Oversized materials housed in Box 33